♪ In the not too distant future ♪
♪ Somewhere in time and space ♪
♪ Mike Nelson and his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught in an endless chase ♪
♪ Pursued by a woman whose name is Pearl ♪
♪ An evil gal who wants to rule the world ♪
♪ She threw a few things in her purse ♪
♪ And in her rocket ship she hunts him ♪
♪ All across the universe ♪
♪ I'll get ya ♪
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ In the worst I can find ♪
♪ He'll have to sit and watch them all ♪
♪ In a monitor his mind ♪
♪ Now keep in mind Mike can't control ♪
♪ Whether movies begin or end ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot who's called "Hairbomber" ♪
♪ On a jib-son-tongue ♪
♪ Check me out ♪
♪ I am Rick ♪
♪ You're wondering how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ Oh mystery science theater, 3,000 ♪
[Buzzer]
This is really fascinating.
Hi everyone, just here with Tom Servo discussing his art.
So you say Crow gave you the money to do all this, huh?
Well, yes. I think he saw in me and my art a kind of truth, you see.
And with his 30 grand plus a matching grant from the Chubb Group of Insurance Companies,
I can finally express myself and put down 59,000 on that stable of Trotters down south.
Hey, hi Mike.
Servo, I just paid the caterer.
It's kind of pricey, but hey, it's the art world, huh?
So, let's take a look at my portraits.
Huh? Hmm, huh?
Hmm, huh?
Wow.
Oh my, wow.
Yeah?
Crow is, uh, huh.
Well, you know, Servo, these all...
paint a stark portrait of a cruel despot?
Uh, no, I was actually going to say they're all kind of negative.
Oh, fine. Why don't you just paint a picture of you in heaven playing golf with clowns?
Now that's not bad. Here, I'll write you a check. Will 30,000 be enough?
I better make it 60. I might want to do an unfiltered.
We'll be right back.
And stab at the canvas.
I, uh, thought you were going to paint me playing golf with clowns.
No, no, you want to do yourself tossing kittens into a meek rinder.
I have my notes if you'd like to see them.
Whoa, whoa, hands, prepare to die!
Wait a minute, Jipsy, let's not jump to any conclusions. What's the problem?
We're caught in some sort of tractor beam pulling us at a million times the speed of light towards an unknown destination.
Time and space are meaningless, and the physical laws are breaking down.
All right. See? Oh, wait. We're slowing down. I guess things will be okay.
I wonder where we are, though. Of course, I didn't know where we were before, so we might as well be here as anywhere.
That's what I always say.
Hello? Anyone there?
Shoo! Get out of here! Beat it!
Please, do not be afraid.
Welcome, and try to comprehend us.
Uh, okay.
What's to comprehend?
Oh, you are to us as an amoeba is to you, for we are the observers.
And we have evolved beyond language.
We are gratified that you understand our words, for we communicate only with our minds.
Wow!
Except you're talking now.
Yeah!
No, no, no, no. Do you see how your comprehension fails you?
For we communicate only with our minds.
You see, we have evolved beyond the need for bodies, and now we are simply brains.
You are as amoebas, but do not be afraid.
No bodies. That is fantastic!
Unbelievable. Well, except you have bodies right now.
Well, yeah, you got a point there, Mike.
Yeah! What the hell?
Naturally, we require host bodies for our self-sufficient brains.
Wouldn't it be more convenient to just leave your brains in your head?
Right.
Convenient? Why, our brains are fully functional for our bodies for up to 50 yards.
Well, they may not understand. They are as amoebas.
Look, when you cut it out with this amoeba thing, I am way more evolved than an amoeba palae.
Tell you that.
Hush, hush, Croce. Who is that grabbing the towsky there?
She is your friend and another of our guests.
We have brought you all here to observe her magnificent experiment.
Though we have acquired all knowledge and have evolved infinitely beyond you.
Hi, Mike. Guess I caught you again, huh?
Hey, what do you think of these characters? Pretty evolved.
She and her companion are our guests.
We will use our minds to create anything they need for their comfort.
Yeah, pretty nice setup here. Dallas reruns, plenty of long necks. Bobo's happy.
Hello, Mike. Oh, this is nice.
Sweet deal, even though I am as an amoeba.
Ha! Oh, please. This is beneath my dignity.
Anywho, your movie today is something called the thing that couldn't die.
Observers, after we're done observing this group, we shall dissect them and display them in our museum.
Other children will be delighted.
Do you think the orbiting ones heard?
Excellent. Send those who are as an amoeba the movie.
Amoeba this. Yeah, get a tan.
Oh, wow!
[Buzzer]
The weather today, the oceans turn black.
The big valley!
A strong thermon story.
Couldn't die or wouldn't die.
Plug it in, Joe.
Ah! People! They've beamed onto the planet OK Corral.
Well, looks like somebody's mama let him grow up to be a cowboy.
Let him play guitars and drive them old trucks.
Didn't let him be doctors and lawyers and such.
Shame, really.
Maybe they'll be line dancing.
I hope not.
Well, this is as close as we can get to the horses. They don't like us.
Well, looking back, it's LA. They're like a block from the comedy store.
Van Nijs.
The big valley!
Joe dropped the needle. Now he's off eating a mellow cup.
Squeaky, we gotta leave. Come on.
Don't you feel anything here either, Jessica?
[Drumming]
You know, we do have running water back at the house, Jessica.
Well, there was a spring near here once.
Dried about ten years ago, I guess it was.
But that vein of water must still be here on the ground.
She'll find it, if it's here.
Yeah, she'll find it.
She can find more than water.
You remember last spring, she found my wedding ring. I lost in the mulberry patch.
The King's Man Approacheth.
This is an early version of the Milagro Beanfield War.
Why can't I just bend spoons with my mind like everyone else?
I keep forgetting that my watch is missing.
Well, we're home before sundown.
You were right, Gordon. It's a wonderful place for a vacation, isn't it, Hank?
It's exactly as you described it, Sonny Corleone, dude.
Even including Linda.
Even the wild boar in the hills.
Look, I'm sorry I told that story.
It's changed.
Jessica was only thirteen when I went away to college.
Now she's twenty-nine. I kind of had a bit of a hard time.
It's like her underwire bra just sprung out.
What is she doing?
Hunting for wire with a fork stick.
Or they're teaching her to fetch.
And I don't like it. Why not?
Makes a beautiful picture. I think I'll sketch it.
He does one of those big-head caricatures.
Why don't you try down by the creek, honey?
You need pintar on this thing.
They stepped in something.
No use today, Aunt Flavia. I'm just too nervous.
But, dear, you were so sure you'd find water.
Yeah, they're all dumb as post and they home-schooled her.
Not when I can feel people doubting me.
Have a nice ride, Mr. Hawthorne.
Wonderful.
Can I interest you in some insurance?
I have a geologist friend who'd be happy to look at it in a well for you.
He wouldn't charge much.
But Jessica doesn't charge anything.
And the devil's built right in.
People are all in there for superstition.
It's not superstition.
Oh, you're wrong, Jessica. It really is.
It's not.
It's hard science.
I'll show you.
Guy's smoking a field mouse.
Jesus.
Ma'am, do we have crops to get in or horses to feed?
Maybe those irrigation lines like we were talking about.
Ma'am.
Here comes the bride. She's out of her friggin' mind.
Na-na-na-na. Mess it up. Mess it up.
What do I do now? How do I get myself into this stuff?
Come on, you stupid stick divine.
Oh, he needs batteries.
Water. She's found water. Hooray!
Boy, go stake that spot.
Come on, Mike.
Doubt my ass, science boy.
You saw that, Gordon?
I don't mean an empiricist, but I need to see the water.
You're my favorite sister, daughter.
Good girl.
Right here. Here's where I feel it's strongest.
Gonna see Miss Eliza.
Go to Mississippi.
No, don't.
What's wrong, Jessica? Don't dig here.
Please don't. There's something evil down there.
Maybe it's gold. The root of all evil.
Come on, start digging.
No, it's not gold. Leave it alone.
May I remark that superstition also leads to delusion?
I'm not having delusion.
There's nothing evil about digging a hole.
Yes, there is. Get to work, Boyd.
Okay. All right, Mike.
You wanna see Miss Eliza?
You're all horrible. I hope you all die.
I hope a tree falls on you.
Kidget. Have you lain with a hornet one again?
Linda.
I hope it rises and falls on you again.
Let's get her to the cabin.
It's like Carmine from Laverne and Shirley.
Her butt is under a big w.
Go on.
Too bad this tree was our state forest.
You're all evil, and I hope you all have snacks.
See?
All I have power over the trees, that's nice to know.
Are you sure you're all right, Linda?
Can you move your hands and feet?
I think it's 'cause of my jeans.
Still in one piece.
'Cause I was more frightened than hurt.
If you were hurt, I'd never forgive myself.
Hey, you can't don't ski.
But Jessica, it wasn't your fault.
It was. You heard what I said.
Honestly.
Think of something.
I can't think you had anything to do with that.
But I did. It was an evil wish.
An evil is very strong.
Oaky beatniks.
Jessica, it was pure coincidence.
A strong gust of wind came and a...
An evil wish.
Who's for evil lunch before I take an evil nap?
I'll never use the witching wand again.
I'm all through with that kind of thing.
So interesting, though.
I think it swings.
When did you first discover that you were a water witch?
There's something Arch Hall Junior about her.
Always.
Have a seat, Cindy.
I've been able to find things.
Like once I found this rubber band.
It's right for me to find that, is it?
What do you mean?
When it's right?
I must do it to help someone.
Like when I crushed your vertebra.
And I can't accept any reward.
There's no offers on the table.
And I must do it of my own free will.
Jessica.
Ever since we pulled you out of that well...
We're only summer guests here.
We're not returning next year.
You were that tall.
The fairy tales are all right for children.
You're a grown girl now.
Girl, you'll be a woman soon.
Oh, no, she's getting squishy.
Come on.
Go on. Do it.
Go on. Get to it.
Oh, look, let me prove it to you.
Linda's watch has been missing for about a week.
As was previously indicated.
If you have this power to find things,
you're going to lose your watch.
If it would help, I'd sniff one of Linda's garments for you.
You don't believe me.
I hope you drop peanut butter on your toe.
None of you.
You don't believe I made that tree fall?
Mm-hmm.
Well, then listen.
Linda didn't lose her watch.
It was stolen.
But not by anything human.
We'll head back in the morning
and get a refund for the rest of the week.
I just don't know what to say at parties.
You can find the watch in a trade rat's nest.
Trade rat?
Look at the base of the oak tree beside Linda's cabin.
In Maine.
You know, the country needs skilled trade rats.
Oh, yeah.
Just got to quick grab the watch out of my boom
and put it by that tree.
She worries me.
Really? Why?
Then stop worrying.
She's just at the age where she likes to dramatize everything.
I hope you're right.
She's coming at me with a skimitar.
Go see.
Oh, my pants.
Every step they cut into my flesh.
Now there's nothing here.
There's no tree here.
Wait a minute.
There's no trade rat, but there is a skilled artisan rat.
Ooh.
Well, that's a rat's nest, all right.
A registered trade rat.
Quite a thief, that rat.
There it is.
There's a car, several stereos, a health rider.
The rat's put in a new crystal.
It still runs.
John Cameron trade rat.
You know what I think what you like, but I think Jessica knows what she's talking about.
I'm beginning to agree.
What do you think, phony beet?
What's this?
There's something the rat didn't take.
The root's grown around it.
It's been here longer than the oak tree.
I can just tell.
What is it?
A charm, and it looks medieval.
On your ass.
Okay, trees start talking.
Easy.
I think we owe Jessica the quality.
[humming]
[music]
Jessica, may I scare you to death?
Decorating like a keg in kettle in there.
Well, I found Linda's watch just as you said.
Just warming my butt.
I knew you would.
A beautiful and gifted young lady,
forgive amount has been treating her like a child.
Okay, I gotta go watch Barney.
I'm going to go.
What is there to forgive?
My dotting you.
I don't know, your senses must be keener than most.
I'm over here now.
Nature seems to speak to you and voices the rest of us can't hear.
But it frightens me sometimes.
Why?
'Cause it comes from hell.
They're evil voices too.
Sometimes they're very hard to resist.
Just don't listen to talk radio.
Here, I'll polish this for you.
We found it in the trade rats' nest.
You had a little tool and dye shop down there.
Well, then it belongs to someone.
I shouldn't take it.
Well, nonsense.
I have an idea this must be hundreds of years old.
It's been in the rats' family for centuries.
Look, this is the Florida League.
The three points stand for purity,
chastity, and virtue.
Crown stands for courage,
and the anchor for hope.
Turn around.
I think I got most of the rat droppings off of it.
Now, people used to believe that such a charm
really protected them from evil.
As a matter of fact, as long as they believed strongly enough,
it did.
So Catholicism is a placebo.
It's beautiful.
Did you keep the receipt?
Thank you, Mr. Hawthorne.
It's like a shield.
Come on, tonsil box!
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
A girl as beautiful as you will need one.
He's hoping it's gonna be a lewd ranch.
Don't call me Mr. Hawthorne.
Call me Mr. Jenkins. That's my name.
I'm gonna go up and watch him dig for a while.
Last week, he gave me a Makita drill.
What's he trying to say?
You see, Miss Liza?
I'm gonna go to Mississippi.
Really glad I wore business casual today.
Ow!
Stop digging, you fool. You hit something.
What is it?
It sounds like metal.
Well, he just hit himself in the back of the head.
Watch it, Mike.
So what have you found?
We don't know yet.
Man, he's good.
He's like he's a geometrical savant.
It's a chest. An old chest.
Get it out, boy. Hurry up.
All right, Mike.
He might as well turn it into a den.
The first nuclear waste depository was a dismal failure.
The Grand Ma of the Baskervilles.
Gold.
It must be gold.
Yeah, the Great Nevada Pirates buried it.
Has anybody ever buried anything else?
Oh, bless Jessica.
She may inherit a fortune yet.
Oh, Mike, break it open.
You think Flavio will fit in that hole?
Sure.
Sure, our busts are open.
Maybe there's rabbits in it, George.
We must damage it.
It's old. It has a history.
I have a history, too.
A history of taking in guests to keep them losing my ranch.
Hit it, Mike. Give him room.
I'm not the loser, fortune. Not find one.
Now, you listen to me, young man. This chest is mine.
But Holst's treasure, that's mine, too.
You're not going to keep it away from...
You have beautiful eyes.
What did you say?
Loser, fortune.
Its value is a historical relic.
Maybe greater than the value of anything it contains.
This is also true of you.
A museum might pay plenty just for that chest.
But not if you smash it with a pickaxe.
Oh, that chest.
Well, how do you plan to get it open?
I'll open it from the inside.
Well, there are chemicals that will remove the rust and vertigris.
Or drag it behind the pickup.
Good Lord.
What is it?
A date.
Oh, wait. I think it's a fig.
1579.
Look at the letters. Old English and the spelling.
If he valuest thy immortal...
Stuff. Things.
If he valuest thy immortal soul...
And you're too close.
Open not this accursed chest.
For within it, life...
My stuff.
Life.
Well, go on. Go on. What life within it?
I can't read the rest until I remove the vertigris.
It's gonna have its back removed.
I know this much.
Only one Englishman visited California in 1579.
Sir Francis Drake.
Oh, wait. Ludwig von Drake.
If this chest is authentic, it's worth thousands.
Of pennies.
But you need an expert witness here when we open it.
Well, where do I find one?
I'll go to Berkeley tonight and get the chemicals.
And to Julian Ash, president of the Historical Society.
You mean to say I have to wait until tomorrow?
Well, there's that all night Historical Society.
I think so. I'm just to risk your immortal soul.
Drive through window.
He's right, Mrs. Magatay.
Better wait. There's no danger.
I'll be glad to stay up and guard it for you.
Well, all right.
Let's take it up to the house. Come on, Mike.
Who's Mike? Oh, I'm Mike.
Sure.
I'd like to see this resort's full color brochure.
Enjoy our cracked staff, Mike, and oily horseman Steve.
I'm back. I carry two of them.
Get to the house, you idiot.
Which tree is the house?
Well, uh...
Hmm.
So...
Yeah, an international coffee's moment.
Jessica, I've been thinking.
You need a little change, a little excitement.
Why don't you come to the dance with Hank and me tonight?
She set the wall for dinner back then.
The girl has to have a partner to square dance.
Maybe Gordon would like to go.
Gordon of Gloucester?
Do you think he'd take me?
Of course he would.
Oh, yeah.
I'll ask him for you.
Please don't.
I don't want you to think that I...
Villagers are coming to get her.
What is it?
I just noticed that window treatment is evil.
Well, they found something.
Please don't let them in.
Sure, I'm an idiot, but it's a medical condition.
No, Jessica. A treasure chest.
Did you measure the treasure chest?
A wonderful find.
I'm almost sure it was buried by Sir Francis Drake.
Possibly part of the loot he stole from the Spaniards.
But of course I studied refrigeration, so I...
Who knows when I get back?
Oh. You're leaving?
Yeah, as soon as I change clothes.
Mr. Atharne.
Meryl.
I mean Gordon.
I was hoping that...
Don't worry about that copper chest.
There's no evil left after four centuries.
What if they ziplock the evil?
Good night.
Hurry back.
Come on, Mike. Put it in the sewing room.
We'll lock it up until morning.
Put it in there with the Ark of the Covenant.
And Flavia?
That flavor-flav?
I don't want it in the house.
Do you expect me to leave it in the field?
I won't stay in the house with it.
But, Jessica, you're acting like a child.
Say what you please.
I won't.
If you feel that way, Jessica, then why don't you stay in my cabin tonight?
Yeah!
Is that all right, Mrs. McIntyre?
Of course it's all right.
Come on.
Chunkhead's never been in the house.
All set, Mrs. McIntyre.
I'm bringing you in for wrestling, ma'am.
Ma'am, as a working ranch, when are we gonna get a cow,
maybe plant a crop or something or...
Well, I'm gonna read my favorite Shakespeare play,
"Major for Major."
There. Good night.
Been a pleasure, ma'am.
I love that.
I'll finish up the chores. You stay here.
How does this chair work?
Already?
Mm-hmm.
Gee, you look pretty.
Oh, thank you, dear.
I meant him.
I'm sorry Gordon had to leave, Jessica.
Why don't you come with us anyway?
There are always extra men at country dance.
Men's seconds, men are regulars.
I don't want an extra man.
You have to build a garage.
An awful old chest.
Yeah, these archeologists are always interested in old chests.
I'll take an artist like me.
On second thought, I think she's safer here
than with an artist like you.
She's right, honey. I take you to the mat.
Bye-bye.
Anything in the place is yours.
Including me.
Oh, come on.
So sweet of him. I really should take him up on it.
[Buzzing]
Careful, Mike. Don't rip the decals, Mike.
You ripped them last time, Mike. Don't rip them, Mike.
No!
What do you want?
I have been sent here by the high one to observe you,
to study your culture and to learn.
Well, how long is that going to take?
Not long, I assure you.
Well, then keep your eyes open in your mouth shut, hood boy,
and keep your grubby little mitts off my stuff. Capiche?
This will not interfere, but an impartial observer.
Yeah, right.
I have made contact, and am observing one of the odd, grim,
marionettes that accompany the biped.
The reasons are known. Someone has shaped this lump of epoxy
into human-like form, perhaps in attempt to comprehend
their own hideous shape. More likely to mock the God
that blighted them so.
Hey!
Jerk!
I shall now observe the ungainly peach-colored creature.
His humid, fleshy extension struggle as he attempts
to dominate some simple, seemingly purposeless toy.
Already a sense of pity overcomes me,
yet I am repelled by my own compassion.
Although his biological makeup implies a living thing,
I am certain we shall discover him to be
but an animated piece of refuse or feces.
But I must remain impartial and continue to study,
even as he mocks everything I hold dear.
I hate him, and can take comfort only in my own cool detachment.
He looks at me now, and no flicker of comprehension
is served in his flat and lifeless eyes.
I can only pray that his tiny spinal column conveys
no spark of truth, no splinter of the horrible reality
that is his own soul.
My God, I pray for his death as to all things
that love, rightness, and decency.
All right, that's it.
I'll try to get the clown hammer, Mike.
Yeah, I got it.
That's white boy.
We cast into this.
Right on the way.
On by Ash.
There we go.
Observe that, pal.
Well, he forgot his Haggis hot dish here.
Well, I think that's his brain. We'll be right back.
Am I getting red?
Oh, yeah, right. How long do you think an oily beat
is gonna last at a country dance?
Why don't we swing by the fleet firm and pick up Ferlinggetti?
Poor Judd is dead.
You know, I'm nothing like smoking a Slim Jim.
If Mike Connors and David Chanson had a baby,
we'd be in trouble.
Evil book, evil sulfur, evil rototendron.
There's a figure hosting on my back brace.
You don't mind me tootin' my own horn.
I am so much more discreet than this guy.
Oh, that's the hey.
The music, the mood, the sweeping romance of peeping.
Well, howdy, ma'am. The kindly peeper.
Old-timer Billy Slater's doin' three years community service.
People will say we're in love.
I could just fly across the English Channel in this.
Why don't you just come on in, Steve?
I love it when she dresses like Billy Burke.
I thought it was Flavia's room.
Sandy Dennis in Butterfield, A.
She took off her dress and now she's less new than she was before.
Well, they got a million kilowatt yard light.
Yep, pretty much saw her slip.
I'm takin' forever in there, and I fall into somethin'.
He's rebooting.
What do you know?
Nothing.
The only man left on the ranch.
We don't need no other men.
We've got each other.
You and me are plenty.
I think so, too.
Stop grabbing that rifle every time I'm not looking.
You don't have to shoot a gun. You'll hurt yourself.
I wasn't gonna shoot it.
I was gonna clean it at you.
If anybody tried to bust in here, just use my hands on 'em.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought you were Dale.
Yeah, you're pretty strong, Mike.
Sure.
Sure, I'm strong.
I bet you could almost open that copper chest with your bare hands.
Sure.
I could do that, but it would be wrong.
But that wouldn't be right, would it?
They're gonna take all that.
The only reason they didn't want you to use the axe is because you'd crush it.
But if you could open it up without breaking it.
Like the lamp wants you to.
I just asked, but this is Mac and Tariff. It's all right.
And you wait right here.
And don't touch that gun. They make too much noise.
You understand me?
I love you.
Did Flavia hire this guy directly out of prison?
Aunt Legubria, is it okay if we open that box thingy?
Okay, cowboy. Hop in. Let's get this rodeo started.
She's got her Nancy Culp commemorative plates up on the wall.
Oh, E.G. Marshall, you are a bold one.
Unfortunately, she decorated her room with blunt instruments.
There's a bright golden hazel.
Wow, they held the tension for a full second.
Oh, Merv. Merv.
Lakers tickets on the floor, man.
And it's jammed with lady shicks, nude pictures of George Goble,
tic-tacs with fuzz on them, and other stuff.
The big guys hurt himself in so many ways since this guy left.
He shot himself. There's a rat trap on his foot.
Fell down the stairs. He's covered with mud and tower feathers.
Tic-tacs.
It's all right with Mrs. McIntyre, just so we don't damage a thing.
She said I could open it?
Sure. She gave me the key, see?
Now move your chair.
I could move two chairs.
Don't go ahead.
But you said she told us we could...
It doesn't matter. Boy, anything wrong?
Nothing at all, ma'am.
And Mike just turned over the rifle.
She's quick with a robe.
Well, time to be careful. I'm trying to sleep.
Surely well. Good night, Diphtheria.
I gotta thank you for setting us up, pal.
You heard what she said.
Oh, I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
From the Jean Stapleton collection of lingerie.
Oh, the hell is Emma always starting to kick in.
Why don't you hit me anymore?
A singer straight-stitched. You know how valuable those are?
When we dug this up, it looked to me like these iron vans were loose.
Let me show you. I got strong hands.
[imitates gunfire]
Let's see. Where was I? Oh, yes. Will, gear.
Oh, Will.
Are you sure she said it's all right?
There's nothing to worry about. Nothing to worry about at all.
You can always put those vans back on afterwards. No one will ever know.
Yeah. Yeah.
As long as no one knows what's on the inside or counted,
who to say if any of this missing.
[cars honking]
Turns out David Copperfield's in there.
Please, no.
Okay, I got that crime going. What else can I get going here?
What a good life.
Ripping off the old lady, making Mike do all the work, peeping.
Yeah, it's sweet.
He's not a very good Civil War reenactor, is he?
I'm gonna penny him in.
Yeah, a little lady ought to be down to her 12th layer of slip-dye now.
I can't wait to be a grandma.
I know. I'll try on the bed.
Sometimes I worry that my lamps aren't feminine enough.
Nice evening. I should really get drunk and hit someone.
[laughs]
Look, I'll stand out here and you can peep from over there.
Her nightgown is comfort rated to 20 below.
The hell, she's just begging me to peep.
This pan-wa is for me and my future husband.
He saw my bustle.
A dramatization of the Lutheran attitude towards sex.
There's a dark oily film on my headband.
My hands are less strong than previously thought.
I'm having impure thoughts about Pat Boone.
Can you do that?
Sam Shepard is Chuck Yeager in Night Mother.
Don't. She's always one step ahead of me.
Is there something Vicky from the Love Boat asked about her?
Yeah.
But I'm alive with pleasure, ma'am.
Fine. I'll try the psychotic virgin down the block.
Thank you, Chastity Amulet.
[sniffing]
All right, my hands suck, okay?
It's a matrushka chest. There's 30 more in there.
Sir Francis Drake's tackle box.
There's a bunch of basserinos and daredevils in there.
Bring me the head of Edward Mulhair.
[music playing]
You're a big one, aren't you?
Dad?
There's a black greasy smudge on my pillow.
I only peep six hours, but I'm gonna put eight on my timecard.
How you guys doing?
Fine. You?
You want a peep or something?
So, after I lost my body, I moved to Indiana, which was totally bogus.
I'm not totally not open there.
Tag, you're at no tagbacks.
Stupid idiot. What's wrong with you?
I'll tell Aunt DeFluvia.
I have a new friend, and his name is Tommy, and he's going to take me to the big place.
One more step, can you?
Worker's rising up against the man.
Suddenly, the knife went off.
Oh, Mike Douglas.
Is this dagger seep before me?
I must carry on his peeping. I know he'd want it that way.
He appreciating the pen knife scene.
Let's see. He glued his knife upright on a coffee table and fell on it.
We were carving soap into figurines, and he tripped.
We were stabbing each other, and he died.
Yeah, I think that's it. That's the one.
Well, why did you do that, you bubble-headed pooby?
Yeah, yeah, I'm getting a drink, oval tea.
And Earl Anthony's got a 7-10 split he's going to have to pick up here.
Well, Aunt Cooley is going to flip when she sees this.
Now you got to support my neck. Support my neck, I said.
Head, meet dead guy, dead guy, meet head.
Now you got to admit, this doesn't look too good.
No.
Oh, and Aunt Scapula just got that from furniture bar.
Oh, goodness, I'll grab my blunderbuss.
Jessica!
[humming]
Jessica, help!
Can you hear me?
No, your voice isn't piercing enough.
Jessica!
Jessica, action hero.
Come on, be cheeks.
What's the matter?
Downstairs! Something horrible has happened! Hurry up!
Okay, you stand there shrieking like a dental drill and I'll go endanger myself.
Oh, it was a mosquito in my room, never mind.
My recipes!
Surprise! Happy birthday, Toohy.
The chest! The treasure's gone!
They took my treasure and I feel displeasure.
I told you it was evil.
Yeah.
Oh, no, not the Sackaroonie sauce!
I... I heard Boyd yelling at Mike.
Then I heard a crash.
You mean a crash?
Mike wouldn't hurt Boyd. He wouldn't hurt anyone.
Of course there were those hollered out cat heads we found in his room, but...
What's that?
Yeah, it's just those trade rats working the night shift.
Well...
It's only branches scraping against the house.
This is no time for your damned high coos.
Where was a London?
I wish dogs wouldn't howl like this.
How would you like them to howl?
You'd better call the police and Flavio.
Because of the dog?
Yes, I suppose so.
She's got Burgess Meredith number on her speed dial.
You just know it.
Not only is this just a telephone dialing scene,
the person dialing isn't even on the screen!
Hello. Brought to you by Anderson Windows.
Hello?
Colleague in man.
Sheriff's office?
Trick or treat!
I'm going as ahead with a big dumb guy carrying me, see?
This is Flavio McIntyre.
Oh, they kept the original woodwork very nice.
Very nice.
They're right from the chest empty and blood all over the floor.
Oh, I'd forgotten all about those.
You are pulling my hair!
Yes, the McIntyre ranch near Cabrio Canyon.
Cowboys doing his Amy Carter impersonation.
Please hurry.
My niece and I are here all alone.
Thank you.
They say there's no way you can get the stain out.
I have the strangest feeling.
Like I'm walking in applesauce.
Is there something trying to overpower me?
Did you have the pesto pizza before, bad honey?
Gordon.
He brought FDR with him.
What is it? What's wrong?
May I come in?
Have you forgotten you dragged me out of bed to see a treasure chest?
I'm sorry.
This is McIntyre, Miss Jessica Burns.
This is Julian Ash, president of the Historical Society.
And my future husband.
What's all the excitement?
The gold.
All the gold that was in the chest is gone.
Well, that about wraps the scene then.
- Good night, B. - Good night, Clorick.
You're doing barium shooters.
Can't understand why the police don't come.
- Main one is a joke. - One way or the other.
It just occurred to me.
I didn't meet anyone when I drove over it.
That means fish prices will go down.
The thief must be on foot.
And still near here.
You can't get the damn olives open, baby.
There's a way we might find a wounded man.
You can tell us. With this.
This dual action marshmallow stick.
Won't you try?
You know, a single long stem stick says so much.
Yes, indeed.
It's the treasure everyone wants.
I can't do it for money. It wouldn't work.
No one said we're gonna pay you. Don't worry.
No. Not money.
Coop outs.
The man whose blood that is.
Boids or mikes.
Maybe badly hurt. The need of help.
The new fiber-filled face.
I'll try then.
But the one should touch something of the thing it seeks.
I finished all the number three.
Cowboy had oil-based blood.
Here, wipe this on your pin-wa.
This scene has powerful asexual undertones.
Amazing, Gordon. Works beautifully.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Watch now.
The stick just slipped in the drive.
You just go and divine, honey. We'll catch up, huh?
See ya.
So she's kind of a Ouija broad.
Oh, man.
Within it lies this embodied spirit of Gideon Drew.
Gideon's Drew?
I don't know.
Look at this man who ever set feet upon Earth.
She's gonna divine herself right over the Walmart.
This embodied spirit.
There's more.
That's impossible.
Okay, here we go. Daddy needs upper mongolia.
Yes! Sit and spin, bird dog.
Sure, go ahead. Take air-coach. See what I care.
Whoa!
Now, Jimmy Boy.
You've been eating me on foul for the Academy days.
Wow!
Who are you?
Designed Jimmy and Speed. Fit again.
Doesn't ring a bell.
You got it on.
You're sticking under, classman.
Come on, Mike. Cleanest clock.
Hey, Mike. Those guys are calling.
What got?
Oh, hello, then. As you may have noticed...
We are using our superior powers to enable you to materialize any person from your own memory.
Are you enjoying your long-lost friend?
Mike, you gotta...
Hey, look. I don't know this guy.
I've never met him before in my life.
Uh-oh.
What do you mean?
We cannot possibly make mistakes so the error must be yours.
Yeah.
Yeah, so just think of something.
Just think of someone else.
Okay, Mike. Quick.
Think of Adrian Barbo.
What? Adrian who?
Animula vegula blandula.
Hospice camescray corpils.
Whoa!
Great crow.
You made me think of the Roman emperor, Adrian.
No, no, Mike. I said Adrian Barbo.
Plain as day.
We know boo in animal snoky.
Boo.
But Mucula.
Mucula.
Rigida.
Come on, Mike. Think Adrian Barbo.
Come on, you stupid orator.
I don't want Adrian Barbo.
Wow.
Hi, boys.
Oh, this time I'm ready, lady.
Come on. This is like a dream come true.
Oh, great movie sign.
Whoa.
Wow.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Adrian Barbo, Mike, how could you?
Come on, she's pounding me.
Pick up some wood.
You know, on a clear night, she can pick up Radio Marti.
This record prepared the 22nd of June, 1579.
Insky Chess Company, Plain to Illinois.
Now you're sure I'm safe up here, aren't you?
And now our national anthem.
Mike. Mike, where are you? I can't see you.
It's one of those hippie outdoor weddings.
Give it to me, straight. How's my skin look?
Eek!
A dung beetle in my larynx, you idiot.
Oh, sorry, my reverb was on.
Are they hoping a ball game will start?
It's not nice to fool Mother Nature.
You know, it's so bright they must live next door to a circle of Ks.
Claude Akin's weight's patient.
Mrs. Muir?
Gideon Drew being found guilty before his comrades of a crime most following
was this day sentenced to a living death.
Wouldn't it be funny if she found divine?
No.
Okay.
So far all I've divine is that I'm freezing my ass off.
She drank like a quart of Robotessum before she came out to divine.
Whoa, it's raining Vaseline.
And she's in the same place.
High hold, high hold, it's off to death we go.
Is it possible that that's a footy pen-roar?
When a leather mug salesman dies.
The old keg of funeral.
Remove the blindfold now and let him see a world where he shall never walk again.
Ah, check your mic, sir.
Quietly, blark. One glance can make you a slave.
Fear not. His eyes cannot abide.
The vision of lost honor that surrounds this ancient talisman.
Remove the cloth.
So they're conquistadors, leprechauns.
I don't know.
I'm back, baby.
Cowards, look at me.
Nay, do you gaze on this?
Oh, it's a tacky.
A lot of cowards from your own heart
fails and visions of the honor you've betrayed.
I, Gromel, hide thy eyes.
But tune your ears to this.
In step, my dear woman.
And they're done dirt cheap.
Yay!
That's your lawyer. I recommend you shh.
No, sir, you're not helping your case much.
Not you guys. You're doing a good job.
So the punishment is yoga? What?
So how much of North America did the elves colonize?
Yeah, got it. Let's go. Come on.
The evil thoughts.
Thy head forever living.
Shall I give this nameless land?
The violence of the rays, thy headless corpse.
Shall find eternity in which to lust
and find the time to shorten, to give it ease.
Great, thank you.
Be thy torment.
Now, Robert Bork's on a tear here.
And the curse shall reign forever and ever.
Until thy headless body join again.
Uh, sir, this is a traffic case.
Strike!
Oh, face in the corner.
Okay, Tom. Nice job on the practice, dummy.
Now let's get the real guy down here.
Now we pack it in dry ice and send it FedEx.
Follow me. We'll bury the body. We'll never find it.
Under Larry Wilcox's career.
Frosted lucky charms, they're magically delicious.
I dreamed I was in a Hollywood movie,
and I was the star of that movie.
I never know where I'll turn up in my maiden form bra.
So she's a narcoleptic somnambulist.
Well, back at it, I'm burning daylight.
His felt-tip pen exploded.
I'm feeling psycho on the soundstage next door.
What at 'em, Rich? What at 'em, Rork?
It's the "We'll Be There When We Can" cops.
Aunt Fischela.
Aunt Flachela.
Aunt Caligula.
I found Boyd dead in a gravy dug for himself.
Wait a minute, miss. Will you explain so I can understand?
I know the place, officer. Come on. Come on, sponsor.
I think the hillbilly's like my reading of Howell.
Jessica, why did you go out there all alone?
This began leading me. I didn't want to.
It's evil. Evil. That's new.
Never, never, never again.
Wait, I want to see that stick.
Come on, Jessica. Let's go into the house.
No. Not while that chest is still there.
It's a good, sturdy stick. Why, I can whip that.
I'm saying, Linda, Jessica.
Aunt Flavio, what happened?
Oh, plenty.
I'll tell you on the way to the cabin. I'm afraid out here.
So, where do you get a concrete sport coat?
That Flavio is one stone, babe.
Well, who are you?
In my heart!
Ash.
Julian Ash.
I'm Hank Houston.
I'm Bob Detroit.
Let's do makeovers on each other till our mom comes in.
Also starring Suzanne Poushet.
There. The door is locked and you're safe.
I'll put on a big stack of Melissa Etheridge,
Katie Lang and Jill Sobuel albums.
I should have remembered.
While I'm wearing this, I'm always safe.
Have you ever seen the children's hour?
Come on, let's get some rest now.
Do you like a man to be a sleep boy? I sure do.
Come on.
Agnus DeMille cops.
Now, that's Boyd, all right.
Any idea who killed him?
I hate to accuse anyone.
But he did it!
You're not accusing anyone.
Just giving information to the police.
Jake and Tad Lamada.
It was with Mike.
Mike?
Who's he?
One of Mrs. McIntyre's employees.
Big fella.
Physically very strong, could wake under the rafters.
You mean a Ness?
No.
Just dumb, but gentle.
That boy treated him.
Boyd was rough on him.
God, he's nursing the head.
Oh, no, no, no.
The body here, homicide, start looking for Mike.
He sounds like the killer to me.
Break our cop-closes now.
Just 'cause me big and dumb, they think me killed Boyd.
Oh, right, me did.
Good idea, keeping a neck-rag handy.
Yep, bear.
Wow!
Dear movie, thank you so much for this scene.
[Knocking]
I guess she ordered an all-night historian, too.
Emily?
I...
I need to do that, um...
Bob Dole, ma'am, where's the outrage?
[Laughs]
It's timely.
Say, honey, can I borrow your hot rollers tonight?
Jessica's asleep.
What is it, Hank?
I just wanted to be sure you were all right before I turned in.
Turned into what?
I'm all right, darling.
The police has stayed until the trouble's over,
so there's nothing to worry about.
All right, good.
Good night, darling.
Good night again, Hank.
Good night again, egg.
[Knocking]
You know, the ranch seems to have taken the murder right in stride.
Yeah.
I've got a lot more going for me at Hank.
Hardware, Hank.
Hmm.
Hank, go away.
I said no, it's a disgusting idea.
Come on, honey, I'll just quietly squeeze in between you two.
Oh, hi, I'm sorry. Is Jessica here?
[Laughs]
Wop, bop, a-lubop, bop, bop, bam, boom.
He's commanding everybody to wang chunt.
[Laughs]
I'm sorry, sir, this window is closed.
Must defrost fridge.
We ought to just pout even in her sleep.
Next time, use your empty hand to knock you, idiot.
You almost broke my nose.
Must drive head to convenience store for smokes and dove bar.
[Laughs]
Uh, uh, uh, Emily, uh, where are you going?
So how do you like my new body?
Hmm?
Peter would tool as Marie Antoinette.
Dude, please kick me again. It's not funny.
Hey, head boy, you left a big grease spot on my bedroom window.
You called me?
K-4 to patrol car GW.
Oh, not a domestic on Walton's mountain.
[Sings]
[Laughs]
We're blocking our roads in that area.
Yeah, that's a productive scene.
You know, his other senses are heightened.
I hear that happens.
When jet jet all way.
We'll keep watching till the rescue crew gets here.
Hold it, somebody coming. Stay on. Who is it?
We have element surprise on you.
Turn on the headlights.
Stop where you are.
It's too late. I'm no longer there.
How droll.
Stop, I said. Be careful. He's cracked.
Drop that knife.
Oh, right at the upper thigh.
Ow.
Ricky Nelson to the rescue.
Put that bullfrog under me. I can't see.
Regret have one life, give country.
No, baby, where you got to go?
But who's gonna milk the horses?
Oh, never mind.
Since I'm so short, it's hard for me to date much.
Now you're safe, and I'm your only slave.
That's the kindest thing anyone's ever said to me.
I'm sorry this had to happen, Mr. McIntyre.
He's not much doubt before he killed Boyd.
There's the murder knife. Try to use it on me.
Speedy-hurst to the rescue.
There's an old hippie driving it with all his stuff in the bag.
Well, folks, you might as well go back to bed. There'll be no more excitement.
Jessica, where's Linda?
I don't know. She wasn't in the cabin.
Wasn't in the cabin?
Neil Diamond.
Oh, God, the historian has a robot.
Flavius said I could sleep over. It's okay.
Can I come out?
I've now officially lost track of how many doors they've gone in and out before.
At least you had it for a while now.
Jessica said you weren't here.
Who's that head on the bed back there?
Of course I'm here. What concern is it of yours?
What concern is it of mine?
I'm gonna marry you, remember?
Is that the guy with the body? Get rid of him.
What's so funny?
Marry you. Marry a painter.
I intend to marry an aluminum-styling man.
You sentimental.
Well, scenario looked familiar, Mike?
Well, unfortunately.
Now I want her more than ever.
Now it's our turn to slap you.
What's wrong with them?
I don't know.
But could you slap me like that?
I don't know. It's time everyone got some sleep.
Yes. Good night, Gordon.
No handshake?
I mean, let's get some sleep on each other.
Why aren't you coming to bed, Linda?
Oh, wow!
This is now officially the best movie in the whole wide world.
Well, I guess I'll just smoke in bed.
I better call Mitch and see how the little Brenda girl is doing.
She's amplishetting the birds.
Oh, I moved your head to the other closet. Hope you don't mind.
I'm gonna put on a skit for you just to pretend we're at Carnegie Hall.
If my mom finds you, we're gonna be in so much trouble.
Big boys don't cry.
I'd like to see her slap him. He'd really go.
And hey, proper magazine up here for me, will you?
Hey, hey, hey! I'm talking here!
[music]
Well, I sure enjoyed my time in the closet.
I was just fluffing up my pillowed hangers.
I was just hosing down my hat boxes.
Yes!
[beatboxing]
Why are you staring at me that way?
You have something in your nose.
I was just admiring the gift that Gordon gave you.
May I try it on? I promise not to take it off.
And after that dream I had when I fainted, I won't.
Huh. Well, I'll be right back. I better nip into the closet for a second.
Oh, help! I rolled off the shelf!
Maybe there's a hacksaw somewhere in the cabin.
I could slip it down around his shoulder, pass through torso.
You know, his work is uncluttered by talent.
Where the hell have you been?
He sold 7,000 paintings to Best Westerns across the nation.
Oh no! 45 minutes of work down the drain!
Remember, you walked into a painting of a door.
I'll just send her my ear.
I know. I'll lure her into a jeweler.
No. I could grease her head and then...
No.
I have got to pop this. I can't stand this anymore.
There.
Hmm. You know, I like the head, but I just don't think we have that much in common.
Seem didn't really pack the while up they were hoping for, did it?
Yeah. Yeah.
Head rolls into the corral. Horses think it's an apple and they eat it at the end.
So there was never any treasure.
If what's written on the chest is true, only a human head.
Hardly that, after nearly four centuries. I'd say it best to only a skull.
There's a lot of tannic acid in the soil around here. It might preserve part of the skin.
You mean turn it into leather?
You rocked my world last night, Flavia.
So if the legend is true...
Ah, they're in the classic "Let's pretend we didn't boink last night" pose.
The head is looking for its body.
Oh please, it's not funny.
Well, I assure you, Mrs. McIntyre, I intend to search for the other casket.
And I'll pay you well if I find it.
You didn't hear anything sneeze in the closet last night, did you?
I don't know why you keep looking at me that way.
That thing around your neck. I want it. I'll buy it from you.
Battle of the network, boobs!
Let me have it, Jessica.
No.
Come on, I promise I won't pit it out.
You like beautiful things, don't you?
Will you keep this dress or anything else of mine that you want?
No.
Do you like bikes?
I'm going now.
How about a nice ironing board? Do you need an ironing board?
Thank you for letting me stay with you.
I bet you'd like a pony.
Turkish taffy.
The earthworms are so loud this morning.
I really get a sense of place here.
Jessica.
I thought you were scared to death.
Come in.
I admire her ability to know where the hell he is.
I'm all dressed to rope doggies and ride the range.
I want to paint you.
No, it's really bad for my skin.
I have to go to my...
The light's exactly right.
Pollyburgin and giant.
Just a quick sketch to start with.
Then I'll drink turpentine and kill myself in the bathroom.
Aren't you a painting lender?
Lender?
Timon.
You're a much prettier subject.
That's impossible.
I can't have you digging up my whole ranch.
Now where are they?
I can persuade the society to pay you $5,000 for each of the caskets.
That's a lot of money, Mrs. McIntyre.
Yes.
Yes, that is a lot of money.
Okay, dig the hell out of my lawn.
And a great contribution to California history.
Or not.
You're thinking that Jessica can help you find the other casket.
Why not ask her?
Oh boy, get her.
Well, I don't want to.
She'll hit me.
After what happened last time?
Well, after all, that can't happen again.
Mike and Boyd are...
This is a great vacation.
I'm sure she'll help you.
She has such a conscience.
Can you believe it?
Where is she?
She and her conscience are in Hague Studio.
Yeah, he's stenciling her.
Just the two of them.
Then they're both in Hague Studio.
Hey, hey everybody.
It's time to debut my documentary about the Civil War.
When did you do a documentary about the Civil War?
Well, I managed to eke out an hour here and there
when I came back from the edge of the universe.
Wow!
Thank you.
As part of my extensive research for my documentary,
or doc as we like to call it in the business,
I painstakingly combed the satellite of love archives.
I call it Crow-T-Robots Bram Stoker's The Civil War.
Did you know that Ken Burns did what many people consider
to be the ultimate Civil War documentary?
Oh, but was it about the Civil War?
Well, yeah, it was called the Civil War.
Oh, like the great Ken Berry,
currying the phrase Civil War.
Okay, let's watch the first installment of my 18-part
36-hour series on...
The War Civil.
Can I buy it, if you please?
[music]
The Civil War was a war that took place
during a certain period in our nation's history.
When exactly?
No one can say.
But no records exist to pinpoint precisely when that war took place.
Young Americans were sent to wage a war
in a country they had never heard of, never seen,
nor much less could find on a map.
Here now, a young bugler's tragic last missive.
My dearest Debbie,
here I am at the Battle of Antietam.
General Sherman is really nice.
There was a really good buffet in Gettysburg.
Well, I'd better go. See ya, Dirk.
Clearly, tensions between Abraham Lincoln,
General George McClellan,
and Neville Chamberlain were escalating.
[music]
Quality.
Oh, that's powerful.
So, I'm guessing the other 118 minutes, those are all credits?
I have to admit, Crow, it was kind of disappointing.
Well, sure.
A gripping, detailed saga of our nation's struggle to rest itself
from the grip of British tyranny isn't for everybody.
But Crow, that was the Revolutionary War.
Oh, split hairs, why don't ya?
God damn it, rock on.
Oh, wow. We'll be right back.
Arlene Galanca?
[music]
Yeah, go long.
She should have caught that, she was right there.
I'll just paint myself.
Why do I make people throw shoes at me?
Yes, she comes now.
Evil, evil, evil, evil.
What is it?
Honey, it's an intervention.
Why does everyone stare at me this morning?
What's wrong with me?
There's nothing wrong with you, Jessica.
We, uh, we have a problem.
Oh, let's get to the point.
There's another casket buried somewhere on the ranch, Jessica,
and Mr. Ash has promised us $5,000 if we can find it.
Yes, that's right.
Of course, I haven't seen you demonstrate your remarkable abilities yet.
You've all been sitting here,
plotting and planning to make me do something I know is wrong.
Yeah, and...
That's why Hank tried to keep me in his cabin.
That's why Linda wanted to take away my talisman.
Isn't it enough that two men are dead?
The rest of you want to die too?
Oh, honey, all I'm asking is that you take that fork, sting it.
No!
There's a wedge between her and Aunt Spatula now.
Yeah.
I hate you all.
I wish you all were...
Swedish.
I'll not stay here any longer.
Hmm, wasn't much of a toast, was it?
Well, that's it.
This is the worst Christmas ever.
No help from Jessica.
She's right.
We'll have to make our own breakfast.
You're trying to make her do something against her will because you want money.
I see nothing wrong in wanting money,
and I'm not trying to rob anybody, am I?
You have a point there, Mrs. McIntyre.
I have a plan.
Well, no.
When I read about dousing,
the ability often runs in families.
You could employ normal archaeological tactics.
Will he me?
Oh, I couldn't do that.
I'd...
I'd look so foolish.
Didn't mind if Jessica looked foolish.
Go ahead.
He-he, Flavia takes a hit.
Take it.
Try it.
You're gonna want to choke up on a little bit. You knew it, just...
You'll need to discipline me first.
Heh.
My vacation dollar was not well spent.
I'm going back to the convent.
It didn't work out with the Von Trappes.
You're really going.
Did you pack your stick?
Yes.
Linda's driving me to the bus stop.
By William Inge.
No, I don't blame you for being upset.
I just want to be sure you're safe.
I'll be safe enough.
I'll go to my cousin.
That's just one favor I'd like to ask.
Will you pull down my sweater and back?
Yes.
But Julian and I were talking about this talisman.
He feels it may belong to the same period as the chest
and very valuable...
Like the spaker chip.
You mean you want it back?
I should say not. It's yours.
But if you could let me borrow it, I could have a cast made.
My chest? That's weird.
Is that a den for amulet?
Shut up.
You put it back.
Thank you, Mike.
You're the only one who can take it off.
I helped you put your bra on earlier too, remember?
It's kind of got that Carol Lindley built-in depressed look.
I'll put this in the car for you.
I'm new at this. Is this sexual tension?
By the way, do you know where the hell you're going?
Oh, you don't look foolish at all.
Oh, sure.
See what I mean?
Turns out she has a gift for finding squishy cow pies.
Maybe I'll just sit down and wait for you, Flavio.
You know, at Flavio, Donna, that looks positively immoral.
I mean, she's licking the stick and everything.
I'll look at Linda.
That was her fatal mistake.
She's combing her elbow.
Oh, it's down, dear. I'll just be a moment.
I'm z-barting my hair.
Such a beautiful day.
I keep feeling there's something evil very close to me.
Man, she's a bring down.
I'm close to you.
I don't mean you, so I should think you'd feel it too.
Well, there's a high pollen count.
I've got something to cheer you up.
Something for me?
I got you a cake from Super Moms.
A gift.
Oh, Linda, you're giving me one of your hat.
Well, it's hat-related.
Go ahead. Open it.
Open it, dear.
Open me.
Next time, punch holes in here for God's sake.
You did? Why?
I have the receipt if you'd like to return it.
Don't you like it?
I'm sorry.
I already have one.
You know, the head must have read that
"get girls through hypnotism" ad in PENTAZZ.
Yes, Linda.
Girl?
I like it very much.
It'll go with my peak outfit.
I'm so happy for you, dear.
I'm not going to leave the ranch.
The ranch is going to leave me.
Something I have to do.
Money.
[whistles]
Honey, put the head away for now.
It'll still be here when we get back from church.
I mean, I never really thought I'd be just ahead.
It just happened, because when I was in junior high,
the other kids would pick on me,
and well, I had a big part and all.
Cake?
Oh, thank you.
It's Flavia's famous forced meat cake.
Jessica, I thought you'd gone.
I stayed because I want to help you.
But we already rented out your room.
You'll hunt the other chest?
Yes, garden.
Go cut a fresh warn for me from the willow tree behind the house.
I'm going to divide the crap out of this place.
I'll change clothes.
Oh, I guess that was her.
I'm telling you I'm staying outfit.
So, then the Conquistador said, "No, that was my helmet."
I love that one.
So, what about you? What is Jessica all about?
Jessica?
Hmm, I want to look evil, but not satanic.
Do you think you might need that?
You'll get my gun when you can pry it out of my cold, dead fingers.
I wonder what made her change her mind.
Well, I suppose after she thought about it,
she realized our request was reasonable.
I'm not sure it is.
The thrilling speculation scene.
Jessica, where are Hank and Linda?
In the cabin.
She looked more like a somewhat racy nun than evil.
I'm leaving you, Fabia.
Can you get out of the way of the fruit bowl? I'm trying to paint.
We're ready to start. Come on.
Have a drink.
Booze. Really satisfying.
Sure.
Look at me. Is this what you wanted? The natural girl?
Yeah.
Whatever.
I guess we're not doing the original blocking.
Here's looking up your neck, oh.
Now come on.
I've made deviled eggs.
Put on a dish towel.
She has a new career finding buried English heads.
The J crew divining dress for week-ends.
I think mother's ready for you to move in now, Flavia.
Okay, who messed with my stick? Someone messed with my stick.
So I guess we can assume that Aunt Rabie's dividing attempt was a miserable failure.
I think, frankly, they could do just as well with a systematic grid search.
No, Mr. Ed broke out.
Suddenly the dividing rod points right to Aunt Flavia's ankles.
Oh, let her go. I can't keep up.
The shot took 30 takes.
I found Fogg.
She's found it.
Shut up.
Well, none of them seem to keep up with Aunt Rabie both there.
I found the this island earth music.
My Pogo stick broke.
But this is where we keep all the old heads.
Here.
Get cracking Aunt Flavo right.
Anybody else gonna throw in here or am I...
My breasts have done their job.
Remember when she was on the actors studio show? She was great.
Oh, really? If I hadn't left my trush in the room, I'd be down there with you fellers.
Gordon, I'm rested now. Let me spell you.
It has an immediate heart attack and kills right in.
Yeah, okay.
That's a really intense scene. I didn't know if the old guy was gonna spell him or not.
Yeah.
Aren't the men darling?
- Heard these haybills, Foddy. - Jessica, what's happened?
You're changing. Not the same girl you were yesterday.
Now you're Tracy Gold.
Yesterday I was trying to do what was right.
I was afraid.
Now I'm thinking hell with it.
Interesting. Go on.
But I'm not afraid anymore.
The big valley.
Can I wish belly over there, young fella?
[laughs]
Now get back to work.
I love you so much right now.
We found it.
They found it so I guess they don't have to go yet.
It's about time too. Let's have some light.
$5,000.
Let's get it to the house.
$5,000 was a lot of money back now.
I'd like to open it without breaking.
I might be able to knock the pins out.
Put some oil here.
It's really a good idea.
You know, I hope it doesn't stain like that mummy last summer.
Jessica, aren't you going to watch us open it?
Oh, I'll be back.
There's something I have to get.
Yes. Get that thing.
Run from women's son. Die alone and afraid.
Yeah, this one feels loose.
Sure, but let's get back to work now.
Horror Incorporated.
Dave?
Here's the wind-up and the screen.
Shaving accident.
What? What?
The party's started without me, huh?
I got this for the top of the tree.
Yeah, I had the drink. I had a couple of Captain Morgan's.
So I...
Well, here. Why don't you try this one on, sir?
I think you'll like it.
I want to use some pipe joint compound.
Testing head. One, two, three.
At last. I breathe again.
Though I am a bit congested.
And you are...
Stop using a jerk to my new boyfriend.
Satan still lives.
Four centuries have not reduced his power.
You guys got a phone I could use?
So this is what mankind has become?
Suburban.
Hugs before the butcher.
Waiting to die.
For Flavia!
A formidable force, the octogenarian, the drunken, the wuss.
Which one of you is first?
Him. Him. Him.
Evil is fun.
After so long a fast, I thirst for human blood.
Can you stand some instant?
You.
But I think your blood is too cold.
And yours has turned to water.
Oh, like your blood is so great.
Your blood shows a recent gamma-globulin inoculation.
Your blood is diluted with the vile stuff you drink.
Everybody pretend you don't have blood.
Yeah.
And you have dried up.
I guess I'll just have a pork chop.
Ah. You.
A skinny young virgin.
Sarah Coventry, no!
My contacts are bothering me.
Just gonna give it one more try.
It's just a piece of jewelry.
It. It. It. It. Hates.
Take over the world, right?
He can't even take over a colonial rambler.
Ah.
Better make sure he's dead.
I am. You don't have to check.
All right.
It would feel sorry for him.
Let's let him out and just hide all the knives.
There. You're happy.
[ Chuckles ]
Wait a minute. How did that get in there, Michael?
What?
Hmm?
Long, Flavious. Sweet Papa, get everything sweet Mama need.
[ Chuckles ]
Please forgive me.
There's really no moral redemption for anyone.
No, it's gonna be a really kind of awkward for an old woman.
[ Chuckles ]
I promise I'll never wake up another dead explorer.
I'll protect us both.
The whole movie was leading up to this shot.
[ Chuckles ]
Brought to you by the Breast Council.
Hi, Breast. Will you work for me?
Oh, you sure you want to do this time?
Absolutely. Puzzle it, Lee.
You see, with Crow under our evil power,
we can command it to perform unspeakable acts.
Like what?
Unspeakable. Mike, what do you need? A dictionary?
Oh, ah.
I can hold still.
Use the Phillips head.
But I don't need tools.
I have these hands.
My heads are strong.
Step it up, you big-sided beef.
I think he's coming.
All right, wait.
There, okay. That's nice.
Oh, wait. Look, my body. Would you get out of here?
No, no, not that way. Wait. Look at me.
Go that way. Get out of here. Go.
Man, I don't believe how thick I am sometimes.
Okay, Mike, just look like the big dumb guy.
Great. That's perfect.
But I wasn't--
Here he comes.
Hide me, then suddenly thrust my diabolical visage
right in his kisser.
Doesn't that help, though, if you're kind of--
Hey, Mike. Say, hypothetically,
if I sent Adrienne Barbeau a box of chocolate-covered raisins,
you think she'd go out with me?
No! No!
What you got there are dead muskratters.
Right.
No, like--
As always, Mike, well done.
I'll get the crazy glue.
I guess Maury's wigs do fall off.
The super intelligent, big-brained, white-faced guy
things are crawling.
Hello.
And you can answer to my chiropractor
because I need proper lumbar support.
Ah, Mike, we need you well rested
for more observations tomorrow.
So in your parlance, 'tis light out.
So all's I'm saying, buddies, you'll catch holy hell for me
if I wake up in the morning feeling crappy.
What is this, crappy--
Oh, well, I wouldn't worry, log-giver.
Actually, this bed is quite comfortable.
As I'm sure you'll find out sleeping in this nice bed all alone,
the whole bed for the log-giver,
and not me in the bed at all.
Not even a trace of me.
Not even one stinking lousy bobo-herrick.
Got them all. A nice, clean bed all for the log-giver
and bobo-sleeping on the floor.
Outside, that's the floor outside,
which would be the ground, technically.
That's kind of funny.
I'll just take this little pillow
and put it right back.
Fluff it up for you, yes.
A nice pillow for the log-giver.
A simple rock will be comfortable enough
for the wretched likes of bobo-g.
Good night, log-giver.
A-hem.
[barking]
Forgot you meant...
I still got it.
Hey, your egghead's got a night canopy for this thing.
[snaps fingers]
[snoring]